RESUME

Divya M Mob:+91- 8446576183 E-mail : divyamnair009@gmail.com

Summary:-

Having 4.6 years of Experience in Industrial Automation Sector (Sensors & controllers) and having <u>Sales</u> and <u>Technical and Marketing Knowledge of Instrumentation Products looking for the opportunity to work in the field to enhance and explore my potential. <u>4.1 Years Experience in Capacitors Manufacturing Company.</u></u>

Education Qualification:-

Degree	Name of the University	Year of Passing	% Obtained
SSLC	G.H.S.School	2004	69%
Higher Secondary Examination in Science	G.H.S.School	2006	67%
Diploma in Electronics and Communication Engineering	Surya Polytechnic College	2009	Distinction with 84%

Employment History: -

M/S. AutonicsAutomation India Pvt Ltd. (MNC-South Korean Company Manufacture)

Period: March 2013 to October 2017

Designation: Sales co-ordinator, Marketing & Technical Support (2013-2017)

- Generation of Purchase Orders and proceeding the same to business clients by E-mails and communicate with clients
- Managing the delivery schedule and issue the deliver challans A/C'S and warehouse.
- Managing all the sales related activities & Responding to sales queries, dispacth, pending status via phone and email & follow up for the outstanding payment.
- Supporting to branch sales team and dispatch the products& co-ordinate with dispatch team.
- Reporting to Top Management of client's company wise daily, weekly, monthly sales report and outstanding status and branch wise sales reports. Reporting to management daily wise stock details.
- Keeping track on clients Sales target achievement/purchase target achievement.
- Keep the record of sales leads, Technical and Marketing Related enquiry's.

- Telephonic and E-mail Communication with clients Regards Products Technical Support like sensors and controllers.
- Telephonic and Email or team viewers via communication with clients to solve the Technical issues.
- Telephonic and E-mail communication with clients/Distributors regarding the new launched products Technical information's, Application, Etc and co-ordinate with South Korea.
- Identifying new Ares of opportunities for lead the genaration.identifyingnew companies and collects the data like mail id, contact no, webiste and share the business offerings and follow-up.
- Distributors meeting activities and Entire Exhibition related works from stall booking and stall design
 Etc.
- Sales & Product Promotions Activities via Social Networks.
- New Enquiry related technical support and covert other make product equivalent to Autonics Make.

M/s.Manufacturing Pvt Ltd

Period: December 2017 to till date

Designation: Marketing Co-Ordinator

- Handling the team and training to the new employee.
- Purchase orders process, Ensure the materials dispatch as per commitment and follow-up with courier.
- Monitoring and assign the works to the team and ensuring the work is completed correctly and on schedule.
- Review the sales operations enquiries on a daily basis with the team, ensuring schedules are met and all tasks are accomplished.
- Handling Customers Complaints & customer satisfaction.
- Follow-up for the orders against Quotation, Enquiry, Samples.
- Reporting Managements monthly wise, daily wise sales reports and review of complaints, quotation
 Samples and submit the reports to management.
- Co-ordinator with regional managers for Monthly wise sales target achievements.
- Price costing related works.
- Exhibitions related works and other events.
- New business developments-Identifying new Ares of opportunities for lead the genaration.identifying new companies and collects the data like mail id, contact no, website and share the business offerings and follow-up for orders.
- Maintain all marketing co-ordinators & Marketing Managers records in IATF Format.
- Analysis of the Indian market competitors pricing.
- Looking all Imports & exports of Capacitors from China, Hong Kong, Srilanka, Germany etc and maintain the records.

Additional Skills:

Outlook

- M.S.Office, Tally.
- Making Power Point Presentations,
- Basic IATF knowledge.
- V-Lookup, H-Lookup, Pivotal.

Skill and Ability: -

- Good Communication skills
- Team handling and Team Work
- Ability to work with flexibility time for organization
- An optimistic, quick learner, self-motivated, self-confident, habitual person who likes to take challenges in life. Strong enough to find solutions on new things.

Personal details: -

DOB : 05/04/1989 Gender : Female Marital Status : Single

Language Known : English /Hindi / Malayalam/ Tamil

Declaration: -

I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear responsibility for correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

Thanking you you're faithfully Location:Pune [Divya M]